

Address: Rio de Janeiro, Brazil Birth date: December 10th, 1992 Marital status: Single Nationality: Brazilian Gender: Female

CONTACT ME ON



https://www.linkedin.com/in/raquellima7



https://raquellima7.github.io/raquel-lima-dev/



https://github.com/RaquelLima7



raquellimadev@gmail.com



+ 55 21 98003-1894

SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails
- lavaScript
- Vue.is
- HTML
- · (55
- Bootstrap
- PostgreSQL
- Git
- GitHub
- Linux

RAQUEL LIMÂ

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Hello, I'm Software Developer with experience in Ruby on Rails, Vue.js, Javascript, PostgreSQL, and using external API. I'm a graduate from Le Wagon programming school.

I've loved technology since I was a child and I believe it can change lives because of this I would love to be a part of that change. As I'm always in constant learning, I'm open to working and learning new technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nobordist

Ruby on Rails Developer | May 2021 - present

Nobordist is a startup that simplifies cross-border transactions between Brazil's digital buyers and online sellers throughout the world, its platform allowing it to ship, track & customs clear one's customs transactions worldwide.

- Activities include:
- Writing and implementing Ruby code using the Ruby on Rails framework;
- Developing back-end components and integrating them with front-end using the framework Vue.js;
- Carrying out troubleshooting in appropriate cases;
- Implementation of system improvements;
- Use of external API to implement in the system;
- Working with relational databases (PostgreSQL);
- Writing tests with RSpec.
- Performs teamwork and tasks alone.
- Familiarity with agile development (Scrum).

Full Stack Developer

Freelance | Jul 2020 to Jan 2022

Worked as a freelancer laboring in several areas of programming.

Accepting out projects in WordPress, building static and dynamic websites and web systems.

Acted on the initial stage from the user experience to the end. Also handled proceeding projects, working as a team or individually.

The projects developed ranged from the creation of a law firm website with a contact page for sending emails, business websites, maintenance, and the creation of web systems.

Skill used in projects: WordPress, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PostgreSQL, Ruby on Rails, UI/UX.

AWARDS RECEIVED

- Won the Onebitcode Hackathon. The winning project was Quick Order.
- Earned a LinkedIn Skill Assessment badge in Ruby on Rails, being in the top 5% of 50.6k of people who took this test.

LANGUAGES



Portuguese: fluent



English: advanced



German: intermediate

VOLUNTARY

TED Translators - Translator | May 2020 to present

 Volunteer on the TED Translators website, participating in projects for the translation of several lectures from English to Brazilian Portuguese.

INTERNATIONAL EXPERIENCE

I studied abroad with the aim of perfecting the German language. Course held at the Tandem Berlin school, residing for a month in host Family with interaction in the language with natives and students of other nationalities.

STRENGTHS

- Flexibility and Adaptability;
- Honesty and Integrity;
- Punctuality;
- Open to work with other technologies.

INTERESTS

- I am a football fan, my team is FC Bayern Munich which I'm a big fan of.
 One of the happiest days was when I visited the Allianz Arena, the team's stadium;
- Also enjoy reading books, watching movies, studying languages, and watching Korean series.

Full-Stack Developer - Working student

Full-Stack Developer - SOS Donations | May 2021 to Jun 2021

Project created with academic purpose at Le Wagon.

Worked on the back-end and front-end. Technologies used: Ruby on Rails; Bootstrap; PostgreSQL; JavaScript and Mapbox API.

- SOS Donations is a platform for making donations, where it is possible to see the profile of charities, reviews of other donors, and view the accountability of completed campaigns where the institution must demonstrate the destination of the donations received. The objective with this reputation system is to generate credibility for the institution and trust in the donor so that they can donate safely.

Full-Stack Developer - Buddieget | Apr 2021 to Mai 2021

Project created with academic purpose at Le Wagon.

Worked on the back-end and front-end. Technologies used: Ruby on Rails; Bootstrap; PostgreSQL; JavaScript and Mapbox API.

- Buddieget is an application that professionals can offer their services and also hire. As a user, you can offer different services, check the location of the person offering the service, filter by category and give a review of the contracted service. On the dashboard the user can view their orders, services offered and services sold in detail.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Full-Stack Web Developer

Le Wagon | Jun 2021

 Le Wagon is a French programming school with hundreds of students in more than 43 cities around the world. The Web Development course 24 weeks, part-time, learning all the skills of a Software Developer. HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, SQL, git, GitHub, and Ruby on Rails.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

The Web Developer Bootcamp

Udemy | Jul 2020

• Learned: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, AJAX, Bootstrap, SQL, MongoDB, REST among others.

UX Designer

Instituto de Gestão e Tecnologia da Informação | Nov 2020

Exchange program in Germany

Tandem Berlin | Feb 2019 to Mar 2019

Mhro

February 24, 2022 Rio de Janeiro